Hi, you guys.
안녕, 얘들아
- 어서 와
- 그래
What's the matter?
무슨 일 있니?
나 이런 상황 정말 싫다
Well, it's just.. It's one of these
situations that I just hate.
마사지 손님이
티켓 석 장을 줬거든
A massage client gave me three tickets...
to the Helmut Peltz Exhibit
at the Morgan Chase Museum.
모건 체이스 미술관의
헬무트 펠츠 전시회야
그 남자랑 자야 되는구나
Now you're thinking
you gotta sleep with him.
No. No. It's just that he gave me
three tickets and there are six of us.
아냐
표는 석 장인데
우린 여섯 명이잖아
- 난 포기할게
- 나도
-I'll give up my ticket.
-Me too.
Okay. That's so generous.
너희들 진짜 기특하다
And I think Ross is generous too.
아마 로스도 기특할 걸?
Great! Then it's just us girls.
좋아, 그럼 여자들끼리
가면 되겠네
-Great.
-Yeah.
- 잘됐다
- 그래
So what is the exhibit?
무슨 전시회야?
It's mostly just photographs...
레즈비언들 발가벗고
엉겨 붙은 사진인데
of lesbian love scenes interspersed
with video games and free sandwiches.
비디오게임이랑
공짜 샌드위치도 있대
Oh, man!
내가 미쳐
-Hi.
얘들아
- 어서 와
- 야, 로스
Hey, Ross, listen.
Chandler got you out of going to the
lesbian sandwich museum this weekend.
챈들러 자식 때문에 너 레즈비언
샌드위치 미술관에 못 가게 됐다
Thanks, but I have plans.
Elizabeth and I are going out of town.
고맙지만 난 약속이 있어
엘리자베스랑 여행갈 거야
- 좋겠다
- 그럼
-That's great!
-Yeah.
오빠 떼돈 벌겠네
Think about all the money
that you're gonna make.
무슨 얘기야?
Why? What?
애 봐주면 돈 받는 거 아냐?
Well, her father pays you
for babysitting, right?
재미는 있는데
이젠 좀 넘어가자
That's funny.
But maybe it's time to move on.
질린다, 그만해
You know, let it go. Stop it!
Besides, Rachel's going out
with Elizabeth's father...
레이첼도 엘리자베스
아버지를 만나잖아
그 양반도 꽤 연로하시거든
so he's much older than she is.
Looks like I'm not the only one
interested in fossils.
화석에 관심 있는 사람이
또 있는 것 같다
그런 말 해봤자 각별한
네 화석 사랑만 들통 나지
All that does is remind us
that you're interested in fossils.
Okay, okay.
그럼 좋아
그 남자 귀에다 사랑의 밀어를
'외쳐야' 하는 레이첼은 어떻고
Rachel's gonna need to yell
sweet nothings in his ear.
-Ross?
-Come on! That's funny.
로스
왜 그래, 웃기잖아
이제 보청기가 필요할 거야
Because he's gonna..
He's got, like, a hearing aid.
쉰내가 좀 나지 않냐?
Because he's all old.
One second.
잠깐만
Okay, look, Ross.
이보게, 로스
Just so you know,
since Lizzie likes you so much...
알다시피 우리 애가
자넬 워낙 좋아해서
I've accepted the fact
that you're dating her.
둘 사이를 인정하기로 했네
Really? That's great.
정말이세요? 감사합니다
Yeah, but then I changed my mind.
근데 방금 마음을 바꿨어
I'm funny like that.
내가 좀 웃겨
So I told Lizzie, now I'm telling you.
엘리자베스한테도 말했지만
다시는 그 애 만나지 말게
I don't want you
seeing my daughter anymore.
Look, I realize it upsets you.
저 때문에 화나신 건 잘 압니다
Yes, it does.
그래, 잘 봤어
But Elizabeth and I are both adults...
하지만 엘리자베스와 전
둘 다 성인입니다
so I don't think there's
anything you can do about it.
맘에 안 드셔도 달리
방법이 없으실 텐데요
I'll tell the university about
your relationship and have you fired.
학교에 둘의 관계를 폭로하면
자넨 쫓겨나겠지
오! 용의주도하시네요
Oh, a man with a plan!
The One Where Paul's The Man
정말 멋지다
This is so exciting. You can get your picture
back up on the wall of fame.
명사의 벽에 다시
네 사진이 걸리는구나
그래, 다 쟁쟁한 배우들이야
He's got all the big actors.
It was so cool when I was up there.
저기 걸렸을 땐 참 좋았지
Me and Jim Belushi would just be
cracking up about something.
짐 벨루시랑 같이
히죽히죽 쪼개면서
I get fired off Days of Our Lives
and he takes me down.
'생의 나날들'에서 짤리니까
바로 사진 내리더라
Now he's just laughing at me.
지금은 날 비웃잖아
Look at him.
That smug Belushi bastard!
콱 한 대 쥐어박아 버릴까보다
Okay. Maybe when they put
your picture back up...
네 사진이 다시 걸린다면
맷 라우어 옆이 좋겠다
they could put you by Matt Lauer.
Look at him just smiling at me.
날 보고 웃잖아
Yeah, I know.
We'd be great together.
알아요, 우린 참 잘 어울리죠
- 참, 얘기해라
- 안녕하세요
-So I'm back.
-Who are you?
저 다시 왔습니다
당신이 누군데?
Joey Tribbiani.
조이 트리비아니요
From the wall?
저기 걸렸었잖아요
이럼 생각날 겁니다
Okay, maybe this
will jog your memory.
어쨌든 내 사진 다시 걸어줘요
새 TV쇼 주인공을 맡았거든요
Okay, anyway.
I'm ready to go back up on the wall.
I'm the star of a new TV show.
-Show me in the TV book.
-It's not on TV yet.
TV가이드에 나왔수?
아직 여긴 안 나왔어요
Well, then it's not on the wall yet.
그럼 아직 못 걸겠수
네, 좋습니다
녹화테이프 갖다드리죠
Okay, fine. I will bring you a tape.
So, now, do you have any
of Matt Lauer's clothes?
여기 혹시 맷 라우어가
맡긴 옷도 있나요?
Maybe? Just ones that
haven't been cleaned yet?
아직 세탁 안 한 걸로
God.
아님 말고
난 미술관이 너무 좋아
I love museums.
-Soaking up all the culture.
-Yeah.
- 그윽한 문화의 향기
- 그럼
-Where do you want to start?
-The gift shop!
어디부터 시작할까?
- 오! 기념품가게
- 그렇지
그 다음에는 점심
-And then lunch.
-Yes, but I can't eat too much.
난 많이 먹으면 안 돼
폴이랑 저녁약속 있어
Paul's taking me out to dinner tonight.
He said he has a big surprise planned.
깜짝 놀랄 일을 준비했대
혹시 자기가 게이라고
말하려는 거 아닐까?
Do you think maybe
he's gonna tell you he's gay?
What? No, why?
뭐? 무슨 소리야?
그 정도면 깜짝 놀랄 일이잖아?
No reason. That would just be
a really big surprise, right?
이쪽으로 통로를 내고
예식은 여기서 진행됩니다
You could put the aisle over here
and have the wedding ceremony over here.
I didn't know you could get married here.
여기서 결혼식도 하나?
This would be a beautiful place
to get married.
- 예식장으로서는 그만이다
- 그래
But I wouldn't put the aisle there.
And I would never have the ceremony there.
하지만 통로랑 제단 위치는
너무 맘에 안 들어
예식은 이 커다란
아치 밑에서 올려야지
You'd have the ceremony
under a beautiful arch.
도와드릴까요?
May I help you?
Sorry. Didn't mean to interrupt.
It's just such a beautiful space.
죄송해요, 방해할
생각은 없었어요
아름다운 곳이네요
여기서 식을 많이 올리나요?
-Do you do a lot of weddings?
-Yes, we're popular.
네, 예약이 다 차서
2년은 기다려야 합니다
There's a two-year waiting list.
Sorry.
안됐네요
Monica, you should put
your name down for this place.
모니카, 너도 빨리 예약해라
What? Are you crazy?
뭐? 말도 안 돼
I'm not getting married.
I'm not even engaged.
결혼이라니
약혼도 안 했는데
But there's a two-year wait.
What if you get engaged in two years?
2년이나 기다려야 한다잖아
2년 후에 약혼하면 어떡할래
여기서 식 올리려고
2년을 더 기다릴 거야?
Then you've got to wait
another two years?
That's four years.
Chandler's not gonna wait that long.
그럼 장장 4년인데
챈들러가 기다려주겠어?
다른 짝을 찾아가겠지
He's gonna find somebody else.
미리 예약해놓는 여자로
Someone who did put their name
on the list.
밑져야 본전이잖아
It can't hurt to put your name down.
2년 후에도 약혼 못하면
그때 취소하고
If, in two years, you're not engaged,
you just don't use it.
하긴 예약해둬서
나쁠 건 없겠지
I guess there is no harm
in putting my name down.
I'm gonna do it too.
나도 할 거야
나도
Me too!
-Really? Who would you marry?
-I don't have anyone right now.
정말? 누구랑 결혼할 건데?
모르지, 당장은 아무도 없어
Oh, Phoebe.
오, 피비...
동정할 거 없어, 적어도
내 남자는 게이가 아냐
Don't feel too sorry for me.
At least my boyfriend isn't gay.
피비, 그건 또...
Phoebe, that's not..
네 남자도 씹어주랴?
Don't even get me started on yours.
접니다, 전에 드린
테이프 보셨나요?
-Did you watch the tape of my show?
-I did.
봤지
-Let's get me back up there.
-You don't go up on the wall.
그럼 다시 걸어주시죠
안 돼, 못 걸어주겠어
-What? But you saw the show.
-lt was very offensive to my people.
네? 테이프 보셨다면서요
그래, 우릴 모독하는 내용이야
Dry cleaners?
세탁업자들을?
Russians. It showed them
as terrorists and villains.
러시아인 말일세
테러리스트 아니면
악당으로 묘사했더군
좋습니다, 보세요
여기 해리슨 포드도 있네요
Okay, okay.
Look, you got Harrison Ford up there!
물론이지
포드 씨는 큰손님이야
That's right.
Mr. Ford is a very good customer.
He brings us a lot of clothes.
You bring nothing!
옷을 아주 많이 맡기시지
자넨 뭐 가져와봤어?
네, 그건 그렇다 치고
'에어포스 원'을 보세요
Okay, that may be true.
But in Air Force One, okay,
the Russians were terrorists and evil!
러시아인들이 엄청 흉악한
테러리스트로 나오잖아요
And plus, he kills a bunch of them.
That's offensive to Russians.
게다가 주인공 손에 단체로
죽어요, 그게 바로 모독이죠
-I've never seen it.
-You should. It's great!
난 그 영화 안 봤어
꼭 보세요, 걸작입니다
여기 정말 근사하다
This place is really beautiful.
I've been coming here since I was
a kid. This used to be my grandma's.
네, 어릴 적부터 오던 곳인데
할머니가 사시던 집이에요
내가 우리 할머니한테
물려받은 건 눈뿐인데
The only thing I got
from my grandmother was her eyes.
I mean, not her actual eyeballs.
진짜 똥그란 안구를
받았다는 게 아니라
사람들 말로는
눈이 닮았다고...
But people say that my eyes look...
Do you wanna make out?
우리 뽀뽀나 할까?
좋아요
Sure.
Are you okay?
괜찮아요?
왜 그러세요?
What's wrong?
그냥 너희 아버지 생각이 나서
Yeah. I was just thinking
about your father.
그래서 흥분이 된다면야
Well, whatever works for you.
아니... 그게 아니고
No.
He just really freaked me out before.
전에 나한테 으름장을 놓으셨거든
우리 관계 숨길 사람이
하나 더 는 것뿐이네요
So we have to hide our relationship
from one more person.
그게 뭐 대순가?
Big deal.
게다가 숨기는 것도
재미있잖아요
Besides, we've had fun hiding it.
Yeah.
맞아
- 저기...
- 왜?
-Yeah?
-You brought protection, right?
보호장비 가져오셨죠?
왜? 근처에 곰이라도 있어?
Why, are there, like, bears or something?
그 보호장비 말이군
맞아, 그걸 깜빡했구만
Protection. Yeah. No, yeah.
That.. That I forgot.
I can't believe I brought two cans
of bug spray and forgot that.
살충제는 두 통이나 챙기고
그 중요한 건 잊고 오다니
-I'll run to the store and get some.
-I'm the guy. I'll get it.
가게에 다녀오면 돼요
무슨 소리
그런 건 남자가 사와야지
가게가 어딘지 아세요?
-Do you know where the store is?
-No.
아니
제 분홍색 자전거를 타고
온 동네를 누비고 싶다?
Do you wanna ride around town
on my little pink bicycle?
A little bit.
쬐끔
I'll be back in 10 minutes. Get in
the hot tub and I'll meet you there.
- 10분 안에 올게요
- 그래
욕조에 들어가 계세요
이따 거기서 봐요
그거 좋지
Okay.
세상에, 이럴 수가
너무 예쁜 집이네요
Oh, my God! What a great surprise!
This is such a beautiful house!
고마워요
Thank you. It used to be my mother's.
This is the kitchen.
여기가 주방
-Hey, Chandler.
-Hey, Joe.
- 안녕
- 어서 와
Everybody's gotta be doing something.
다들 놀고 먹진 않는군
You've reached Monica and Chandler's.
모니카와 챈들러의 집입니다
If you're listening to this message,
we're probably screening.
이 메시지가 들린다면
일부러 안 받는 거예요
그래, 맞아
Yeah, we are.
모건 체이스 미술관의
힐디라고 합니다
Hi, this is Hildy
from the Morgan Chase Museum.
I'm calling for Monica Geller. I wanted to
let her know that there was a cancellation.
모니카 겔러 양께
전할 말이 있어요
예약이 하나 취소됐는데
지금도 저희 시설에서
빙 씨와 예식을 올리고 싶다면
If she's still interested in having the
Bing-Geller wedding in our facility...
...it is available..
이쪽으로 연락주세요
This is Chandler Bing!
제가 챈들러 빙입니다
Yes, the groom.
네, 신랑이요
아뇨, 신랑이라니
No, not the groom!
It's so secluded up here.
여긴 정말 한적하네요
I know. That's why I like it here.
맞아요
그래서 여기가 좋아요
I feel like we're the only two people
in the world.
세상에 우리 둘만
있는 것 같아요
어머, 죄송해요
Sorry.
꺄악!
What's the matter, honey?
왜 그래요?
-Did you see a little mouse?
-No! Big bear! Big bear outside!
생쥐라도 봤어요?
아뇨, 커다란 곰이에요
I think I..
바깥 좀 살펴보고 올래요?
-Actually, would you go check on that?
-We don't have any bears here.
여기 곰 같은 건 없는데
Well, okay.
네, 알았어요
Would you get me a Diet Coke?
나 다이어트콜라
한잔 갖다 줄래요?
-Okay. Be right back.
-Okay.
좋아요
- 기다려요
- 네
-What are you doing here?
여기서 대체 뭐하는 거야?
- 너야말로 여긴 웬일인데?
- 난 폴이랑 왔어
-I came with Paul!
-Yeah. I recognized the ankles.
그래, 발목 보고 알았다
-Where is Elizabeth?
-She's at the store.
엘리자베스는 어디 있어?
가게에 갔어
뭐? 여자를 가게에 보냈어?
-You make the girl go to the store?
-Do I know where the store is?
내가 가게 위치를 아나?
Hurry up. Get out.
빨리 나와
Here you go, honey.
여기 있어요
고마워요
-Thank you!
-Diet Coke.
다이어트콜라
어? 얼음이 없네
Ice.
I need ice.
얼음 있으면 좋겠다
Okay.
알았어요
-Thank you.
-Be right back.
고마워요
- 잠깐만
- 네
Okay.
You and your ice.
그 놈의 얼음 타령
Get out! Get out! Go! Come on!
빨리 나와
자, 어서 나오라니까
빨랑
No, not in there! Not in there!
He's in there!
거긴 안 돼!
그 사람 있어!
-Did you really hear a bear?
-Go!
진짜 곰 소리 들었냐?
들어가
Here you go, honey.
나왔습니다
One Diet Coke with ice.
얼음 넣은 다이어트콜라
고마워요
Thank you.
I am so happy that you're here.
당신이 와줘서 너무 기뻐요
다녀왔어요
-Here I am!
-Elizabeth!
엘리자베스
Look! Elizabeth's here!
이런, 엘리자베스가 왔네?
누구한테 인사한 거냐
Who were you talking to?
You guys?
두 분이요
How did you know we were here?
우리가 있는 건 어떻게 알고
아마 차고 안으로 들어간
타이어자국을 본 모양이죠
She obviously saw the tire tracks
leading up to the closed garage.
Obviously.
맞아요
엘리자베스
What are you doing here?
네가 여긴 웬일이냐
Did you come up here to work on
that term paper or something?
혹시 학기말 리포트인가
뭔가 쓰려고 온 거 아냐?
Yeah.
네, 그래요
Well, why don't you go in that room
and do your homework?
그럼 저 방에 들어가서
숙제하지 그러니?
I wouldn't do it in there.
That's my dad's bedroom.
저 방은 안 돼요
아빠 침실이거든요
That's your dad's bedroom.
저기가 아빠 침실이구나
저기가 아빠 침실이었어!
That's your dad's bedroom!
Why are you yelling?
왜 소리를 치죠?
콜라기운이 확 올라오네, 우!
That Diet Coke, I think,
just straight to my head!
Hi, honey.
나 왔어
See you later.
잘 있어
Wait. I bought groceries.
I was gonna make you dinner.
저녁 해주려고 장봐왔어
Well, next time, ask!
다음엔 물어보고 해
Or at least wait for me to ask!
내가 부탁하길 기다리든가
Hi, this is Hildy
from the Morgan Chase Museum.
모건 체이스 미술관의
힐디라고 합니다
-I'm calling for Monica Geller.
-Oh, no.
모니카 겔러 양께
전할 말이 있어요
안 돼
I wanted to let her know
that there was a cancellation.
예약이 하나 취소됐는데
지금도 저희 시설에서
빙 씨와 예식을 올리고 싶다면
If she's still interested in having
the Bing-Geller wedding in our facility...
it is available....
- 제발...
- 이쪽으로 연락주세요
들었으면 안 되는데
Please. He didn't hear it!
This is Chandler Bing!
제가 챈들러 빙입니다
No!
안 돼!
Can I help you?
뭘 도와드릴까요?
저 벽에 사진 거는
아저씨 어디 있죠?
Yeah, where's the guy who decides
whose pictures go up on the wall?
-He's not here right now.
-You're kidding me!
지금 안 계신데요
이를 어쩌나
Make sure you tell him that Joey Tribbiani
stopped by to drop off all these clothes.
조이 트리비아니가 들러서
이 옷 맡겼다고 전해주세요
I'm an actor. I'm trying to get
my picture on the wall.
난 배우인데 저 벽에다
내 사진을 걸어야겠어요
벽에다 사진 거는 사람
또 있는데요?
You know, there are two people
who could get your picture up there.
Oh, really?
그러십니까?
Well, maybe you and I go out
for drinks.
우리 언제 한 잔 할래요?
You're the other one, right?
아가씨가 그 사람 맞죠?
So, Lizzie, are you planning on
staying the night?
그럼 너 오늘 여기서
자고 갈 거냐?
아뇨, 되도록 빨리 사라질게요
No, no. Believe me,
I'm leaving as soon as possible.
좋아, 그래야지
Good. Not that we don't want you
to stay. Obviously, you're welcome.
물론 네가 여기 있는 게
싫다는 뜻은 아니다
How much more homework
do you have?
숙제는 얼마나 남았니?
도저히 안 풀리는 문제가
딱 하나 남았어요
I just have one problem left
that I do not know how to solve.
Rachel, maybe you wanna come
upstairs and help me figure it out?
레이첼, 올라가서
저 좀 도와줄래요?
Really?
내가?
Okay.
그래
Okay, I'll go upstairs...
좋아, 올라가지 뭐
if you get me something
from the car.
대신 차에 가서
뭐 좀 갖다 줄래요?
What do you need from the car?
뭐가 필요하죠?
Surprise me.
나 놀라고 싶어
Okay.
- 알았어요
- 좋아요
So you're gonna be in the car!
I will be upstairs!
당신은 차, 난 위층
그럼 각자 위치로!
That's where everybody's gonna be!
침착해라, 폴
아주 잘하고 있어
Just relax. Relax, Paul.
You're doing great.
She likes you.
레이첼은 널 좋아해
I think she likes you. She likes you.
분명히 널 좋아한다니까
You know why?
Because you're a neat guy.
왜냐면 넌...
쌈빡한 남자니까
You are the man.
넌 사나이야
You are the man!
사나이 중의 사나이!
Still got it.
아직 쓸만해
Still sexy.
여전히 섹시하고
나는야 러브머신
You're just a love machine.
너만을 위해 작동해
헤이, 베이비
Showtime.
작전 개시
나는야 러브머신
헤이, 베이비
-Phoebe?
-Yeah?
- 피비
- 응?
-Have you seen Chandler?
-No, why?
챈들러 봤어?
아니, 왜?
The museum called and said
that there was a cancellation...
미술관 직원이 전화했는데
예약 하나 취소됐다면서
and that we could move up our
wedding. And Chandler heard.
결혼식 앞당기라는 얘길
챈들러가 들어버렸어
I know. How bad is this?
그래, 이걸 어떡하니?
Well, with a regular guy, it's bad.
With Chandler, oh, dear God!
보통 남자한테도 충격이지만
챈들러한테는 '엄마야! '겠지
I know! And he totally freaked out.
I can't find him anywhere!
알아, 제정신이 아닐 텐데
어디 갔는지 모르겠어
-What are you gonna do?
-I'm never going to listen to you again.
어떡할 거야?
내가 다시는
너희들 말 듣나 봐라
"What harm can it do
if you put your name down?"
'밑져야 본전이잖아'
-Rachel said that.
-Well, Rachel's not here!
그 말은 레이첼이 했어
레이첼은 여기 없잖아!
You really think she put
your picture up already?
그 여자가 사진을 걸었을까?
Did she put my picture up?
그걸 말이라고 해?
You kidding, after the date we had?
얼마나 멋진 데이트였는데
I wouldn't be surprised if she put
10 of my pictures up there.
아마 열 장은 걸었을 거다
Except for the fact that I only gave her one.
I don't know where she'd get the other nine.
물론 내가 준 건 한 장이지만
아홉 장은 알아서 구했겠지
Here it is!
여기가 맞지?
왜 '개자식'이라고 사인했어?
Joey, why did you sign it
"son of a bitch"?
개자식
-I didn't do that. Who would do that?
-Son of a bitch!
난 아닌데 누가 이랬지?
이 개자식아
Okay. Maybe ask this guy.
저 아저씨한테 물어보자
-You! Get out of my shop!
-What did he do?
너, 여기서 당장 꺼져
얘가 뭘 어쨌는데요?
내 마누라랑 놀아났어
-He went out with my wife!
-Joey!
조이!
전 아저씨 부인이랑
놀아난 적 없어요
I did not go out with your wife! Okay?
I went out with her.
저 여자를 만났죠
That's my wife!
그니까 내 마누라네
제 손가락을 잘 보세요
저 여자 말입니다
I'm not pointing at her, no.
I'm pointing at her.
"Zelda McMurray."
젤다 맥머레이
Who the hell..?
How did she get up there?!
어떻게 저 사진이 걸렸죠?
Get out!
나가
- 가야겠다
- 그래
-Well, we should go.
-Yeah.
Ross?
로스?
Elizabeth!
엘리자베스...
그래, 좋아
Okay. I'm gonna go out this window.
난 이 창문으로 나갈 테니까
I'll meet you at the front door.
Tell them you're going home.
좀 있다 현관 앞에서 만나
아빠한테는 집에 간다고 해
알았어요
-Okay.
-Wait! No, don't go in there!
잠깐, 거긴 들어가지 말아요
나 음료수나 한 잔 더 줘요
Don't go in there!
I need another soda!
로스!
Ross!
맙소사, 로스
너 대체 여기서 뭐하니?
Oh, my God, Ross!
What in heaven's name are you doing here?
이런 연고로 우린 더 이상
만나면 안 되는 것이야
And that is why
we cannot see each other anymore.
Ross, you and I are gonna have
to have a little talk.
로스
우리 잠깐 얘기 좀 하지
-Daddy, I..
-You're next!
- 아빠...
- 다음은 너야
좋아요, 전 교수님
여기 계신지 몰랐어요
Okay. I didn't know he was here.
Let me just see if I got this straight.
정리를 한번 해볼까?
I tell you to stay away from
my daughter or I'll have you fired.
내 딸을 또 만났다간
해고될 거라고 했는데
What you heard was:
"Take my daughter...
자넨 한술 더 떠서
저 애랑 내 별장에 같이 와서
레이첼과의 주말을 망쳤구만
come up to my country house
and ruin my weekend with Rachel."
-Please, Paul. Just let me explain.
-No! Let me explain! Fired!
제 말 좀 들어보세요
아니, 내 말을 들어
해고됐수
Okay, fine. Fine. Have me fired.
네, 좋습니다
해고시키세요
But I want you to know...
하지만 이건 알아두시죠
that you and I are not
all that different. I mean...
선생님과 전 별로
다르지 않습니다
다시 말하자면...
I, too, am a "neat guy."
저도 '쌈빡한 남자'니까
What?
뭐?
And I, too...
그리고 저 역시
'러브머신'이지요
am "just a love machine."
로스
-Let me show you the guest room.
-Okay.
손님용 침실로 안내하지
I'm so sorry.
Please stop freaking out.
정말 미안해
제발 놀라지 마
I'm not freaking out.
나 안 놀랬어
Why would I? A woman named Hildy called
and said we were getting married.
내가 왜 놀라나?
힐디란 여자가 우리 결혼식
얘기하는 건 늘 있는 일인데
But that happens every day.
Honey, we were at
this beautiful place...
자기야...
거기가 너무 아름다워서
and I just put our names down for fun.
재미로 우리 이름을 올린 거야
잘못될 것도 없잖아
-I mean, what's the harm in that?
-Right here.
여기가 잘못되지
Please don't think I was trying
to pressure you.
절대 부담 주려고 그런 거 아냐
-Phoebe and Rachel thought..
-Phoebe and Rachel?
- 피비랑 레이첼이 하도..
- 피비랑 레이첼?
So the people that knew about
our wedding before me were you...
그니까 우리 결혼식을 나보다
먼저 알고 있는 사람이 너하고...
Phoebe and Rachel, Hildy, and some
band called the Starlight Magic Seven...
피비와 레이첼, 힐디
'작은 별 7형제'란 밴드까지
참, 걔네들 시간 된다더라
who are available, by the way.
It was a mistake.
실수였어
Please don't take this to mean
anything, because it doesn't.
심각하게 받아들이지 마
아무 의미도 없으니까
Okay.
알았어
Really?
정말?
Yes. If it really doesn't mean anything,
because you know I'm not ready.
만약 무슨 뜻이 있었다면
알다시피 난 아직 준비가...
I know.
알아
안다니까
Okay.
좋아
All right.
조이한테 너 돌아왔다고
알려줘야겠다
I'm gonna go tell Joey
that you're back.
네 걱정 많이 했거든
We were really worried about you.
And that guy that
never delivered his burrito?
부리토 배달 안 해주는
사람 있잖아?
He thought there was
some sort of connection.
조이는 그 남자를 의심했어
Did she buy it?
얘, 속아넘어갔니?
Totally.
감쪽같이
-So did Hildy show you the place?
-Yeah. It's beautiful.
그 미술관 구경했어?
그래, 정말 아름답더라
I can't believe
you're gonna ask Monica to marry you.
네가 모니카한테
청혼을 한다니
I know.
그러게
-Hey, Gunther.
-Take these cappuccinos to table 11.
저 왔어요
이 카푸치노는 11번으로 가고
저 손님은 비스코티를 찾는군
And that guy wants some biscotti.
난 커피 한 잔
사가려고 온 건데
I just actually came in
for a cup of coffee.
Do you still work here?
자네 아직 여기서 일하나?
No. I quit a long time ago.
아뇨, 옛날에 그만뒀죠
Did I forget to tell you that?
I'm sorry.
말 안 했다면 죄송해요
-Cool. I was gonna fire you anyway.
-Great!
괜찮아, 어쨌든
짜를 생각이었어
잘됐네요